Marcel Breuer Papers
Marcel Breuer Papers
- Project records
  - HARNISCHMACHER APARTMENT, Wiesbaden, Germany (1929). Marcel Breuer, Architect. [Interior]
    - Drawings, 54
      - Schiebbare Ablegebretter (Nr. 112) [Leaf 96] (4 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Arbeitszimmer-Schrank (Nr. 113) [Leaf 97] (5 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Bett, Schuh, und Nachtschrank (Nr. 114) [Leaf 98] (5 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 23)
      - Glasvitrine (Nr. 115) [Leaf 99] (5 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Likörschrank (Nr. 116) [Leaf 100] (10 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Glasschrank (Nr. 117) [Leaf 101] (10 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 23)
      - Tische im Speisezimmer (Nr. 118) [Leaf 102] (10 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 23)
      - Küchenschrank für Schürzen etc. (Nr. 120) [Leaf 104] (13 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Küchentisch 130 x 60 (Nr. 121) [Leaf 105] (13 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Arbeitszimmerschrank (Nr. 122) [Leaf 106] (16 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Küchenschrank mit Gemüseputztisch (Nr. 123) [Leaf 107] (17 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Besenschrank (Nr. 124) [Leaf 108] (17 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Küchenschränke (Nr. 125) [Leaf 109] (18 Apr 1929), working drawings (originals); 1 (Tube 1317)
      - Vorräte- und Gewürzschrank (Nr. 126) [Leaf 110] (19 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Mappenschrank (Nr. 127) [Leaf 111] (20 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Chaiselongue Schrank (Nr. 128) [Leaf 112] (20 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Chaiselonguebank (Nr. 129) [Leaf 113] (21 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Kleiderschrank (Nr. 131) [Leaf 115] (21 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Wäscheschrank (Nr. 132) [Leaf 116] (22 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Bett (Nr. 133) [Leaf 117] (22 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 23)
      - Linker Nachtschrank (Nr. 134) [Leaf 118] (22 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 23)
      - Rechter Nachtschrank (Nr. 135) [Leaf 119] (22 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 23)
      - Schuhschrank (18 Paar) (Nr. 136) [Leaf 120] (22 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Flurschrank (Nr. 137) [Leaf 121] (22 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Flur Schränke (Nr. 138) [Leaf 122] (23 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Grundriss (Nr. 139) [Leaf 123], working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Bett Damenzimmer (Nr. 141) [Leaf 125] (25 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Bett Herrenzimmer (Nr. 142) [Leaf 126] (25 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 23)
      - Türkonstruktion (Nr. 144) [Leaf 128] (28 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 3)
      - Wandabwicklungen Speise-, Herren-, Wohnzimmer (Nr. 145) [Leaf 129] (28 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Abwickelungen Küche, Anrichte, Flur (Nr. 146) [Leaf 130] (29 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Wandabwicklung Schlafzimmer (Nr. 147) [Leaf 131] (29 Apr 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Grundriss (Nr. 149) [Leaf 133] (2 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Chaiselonguebank (Nr. 152) [Leaf 136] (6 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Wohnzimmertisch 90x90x60 (Nr. 154) [Leaf 138] (6 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Schränke Im Wirtschaftszimmer (Nr. 155) [Leaf 139] (7 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Tisch Wirtschaftszimmer (Nr. 156) [Leaf 140] (8 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Bügelbrett Wirtschaftszimmer (Nr. 157) [Leaf 141] (8 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Wandabwickelung Vorraum (Nr. 158) [Leaf 142] (8 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 23)
      - Tisch in der Anrichte (Nr. 159) [Leaf 143] (8 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Schuhanzieher (Nr. 160) [Leaf 144] (10 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Wintergarten (Nr. 161) [Leaf 145] (13 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Radioschrank (Nr. 163) [Leaf 147] (17 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Schema der Neukonstr. des Schlafzimmers (Nr. 165) [Leaf 149] (24 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 1)
      - Türen zur Terrasse (Nr. 166) [Leaf 150] (24 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 2)
      - Schreibtisch Frl. Berndt (Nr. 167) [Leaf 151] (25 May 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 7)
      - Lautsprecher (Nr. 170) [Leaf 154] (6 Jul 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 2)
      - Lautsprecher (Nr. 170a) [Leaf 155] (8 Jul 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 2)
      - Umänderung zu Zeichnung 123 (Nr. 182) [Leaf 156] (14 Jul 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 2)
      - Stoffarmlehnstuhl (Nr. 207) [Leaf 180] (22 Aug 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 2)
      - Stoffarmlehnstuhl (Nr. 212) [Leaf 185] (29 Aug 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 2)
  - HARNISCHMACHER HOUSE I, Wiesbaden, Germany (1933-1935). Marcel Breuer, Architect. [Residential, Single]
    See also Harnischmacher Apartment; Harnischmacher House II; Harnischmacher Office; Professional Papers: Correspondence: Harnischmacher, Paul and Marianne.
    - Project files
      - Project description, typewritten manuscript, 1 pg.; in German (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Published material, See Professional Papers: Scrapbooks and clippings: Blue scrapbook (2).
    - Photographs, 72
      - Armchair from study, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Breuer in living room chair, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Detail of cable support, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Dining room, finished project, interior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Floor plan [Slide 216], drawings, plan; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - Floor plans, drawings, plan; black and white photographs; 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Front entrance canopy with Marianne Harnischmacher in window, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Glass door to terrace from study, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Group dining in the garden, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Interior stairs to upper level, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Kitchen, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Living room, finished project, interior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Living room [Slide 213], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; duplicate; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - Living room from dining room, finished project, interior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Living room wall unit and armchair, finished project, interior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Living room wall unit and armchair [Slide 742], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; duplicate; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - Living room wall unit and armchair, long view [Slide 354], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - Living room wall unit with flower arrangement [Slide 741], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - Living room window with flower arrangement, finished project, interior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Marianne Harnischmacher descending west terrace stairs, finished project, exterior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - Marianne Harnischmacher looking out of bedroom window, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Pottery display cabinet, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Side elevation with view of service yard [Roll 3, Frame 2], finished project, exterior view; negative; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Side elevation with view of service yard [Roll 3, Frame 3], finished project, exterior view; negative; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Second bedroom, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Second bedroom table and mirror, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - South terrace columns, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - Study with reclining chair, finished project, interior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 4 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Study with reclining chair [Slide 584], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; duplicate; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - Study with reclining chair and armchair, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Upper terrace column and railing, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - View of bocce ball court beneath south terrace, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - View of dining room terrace from above, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - View of façade from below with blinds extended, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - View of house from south terrace, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - View of house from south terrace, finished project, exterior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - View of house from south terrace [Slide 123], finished project, exterior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - View of House from terrace [Slide 214], finished project, exterior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - View of house from the garden, finished project, exterior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - View of house from the south, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - View of house from the southwest, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - View of lower terrace from living room window with flower arrangement in foreground, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - View of lower terrace from living room window with flower arrangement in foreground, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - View of lower terrace from living room window with flower arrangement in foreground [Slide 426], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - View of lower terrace from living room window with flower arrangement in foreground [Slide 744], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - View of south terrace stairs, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - View of South terrace with glass wall beneath, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - View of terrace and building façade from ground level, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - View of terrace and building façade from ground level [Slide 362], finished project, exterior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - View of terrace and building façade from ground level [Slide 591], finished project, exterior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - View of upper terrace from above [Slide 215], finished project, exterior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - View of upper terrace from above [Roll 3, Frame 1], finished project, exterior view; negative; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of upper terrace from above [Roll 3, Frame 4], finished project, exterior view; negative; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of upper terrace from above [Roll 3, Frame 5], finished project, exterior view; negative; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of upper terrace from above [Roll 3, Frame 6], finished project, exterior view; negative; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of upper terrace from southeastern bedroom, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - View of west terrace stairs, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - Work table, wall unit and bookshelves, finished project, interior view; black and white photographs (duplicates); 2 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - HARNISCHMACHER HOUSE II, Wiesbaden, Germany (1953-1955). Marcel Breuer, Architect; Wilhelm Neuser, Associated Architect. [Residential, Single]
    See also Harnischmacher Apartment; Harnischmacher House I; Harnischmacher Office; Professional Papers: Correspondence: Harnischmacher, Paul and Marianne.
    - Drawings, 45
      - Rough sketches: Plans and miscellaneous details, design development drawings (originals); 14 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Gemarkung Wiesbaden (4 Aug 1953), site surveys (reproductions); 1 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Lageplan (5 Aug 1953), site surveys (reproductions); 1 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Construction set (12 Feb 1954): Plans, framing and basement diagrams (Dwg. No. 1); elevations (Dwg. No. 2); wall sections and details (Dwg. No. 3), working drawings (originals); 3 (Tube 576)
      - Fireplace details (15 Jun 1954), working drawings (originals and reproductions); 1 original and 1 blueprint; 2 (Tube 576)
      - Anordnung der Rauchrohre [Ventilation Plan] (May 1954) (Wilhelm Neuser, Architect), C (reproductions); in German; 1 (Tube 576)
      - Erdgegeschoss (Mar 1954), working drawings (reproductions); annotated print; in German; 1 (Tube 576)
      - Garten Harnischmacher: Vogeltranke [12 Jan 1954], design development drawings (originals); in German; 1 (Tube 576)
      - Garten Harnischmacher: Studie 1 (14 Jan 1954), design development drawings (originals); in German; 1 (Tube 576)
      - Window details, design development drawings (originals); in German; 1 (Tube 576)
      - Preliminary scheme (7 May 1953): Perspective, elevations and plan, design development drawings (originals); 3 (Tube 576)
      - Preliminary scheme (16 Jun 1953): Perspective, elevations and plan, design development drawings (originals and reproductions); includes original sketches, original set and annotated reproductions; 10 (Tube 576)
      - Preliminary scheme (18 Aug 1953): Elevations and plan, design development drawings (originals and reproductions); 2 originals and 1 reproduction of elevations; 3 (Tube 576)
      - Preliminary scheme (9 Dec 1953): Elevations and plan, design development drawings (originals and reproductions); 2 originals and 1 reproduction of elevations; 3 (Tube 576)
    - Project files
      - Awards (Aug 1955-Dec 1955), Auszeichnung Vorbildlich Gestalteter Neubauten in Wiesbaden; in German (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Associated architect (Jul 1953-May 1954), Wilhelm Neuser; in German (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Client (Jan 1953-May 1956), Paul and Marianne Harnischmacher; in German and English (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Various suppliers and service providers (1954), includes invoices. (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Office records, miscellaneous notes and sketches (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Shop drawings, product literature and samples, with annotations (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Transmittals (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, 11
      - Bird bath, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Entrance, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Entrance [Slide 781], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Harnischmacher and house, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Harnischmacher and house, finished project, exterior view; copy negative; 1 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - View of elevation from garden with Paul Harnischmacher [Slide 782], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of elevation from garden with Paul Harnischmacher [Slide 783], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of terrace from garden [Slide 784], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of terrace with Paul Harnischmacher [Slide 787], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View out from terrace [Slide 785], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View out from terrace [Slide 786], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-14)
  - HARNISCHMACHER OFFICE, Mainz, Germany (1929). Marcel Breuer, Architect. [Interior]
    See also Harnischmacher Apartment; Harnischmacher House I; Harnischmacher House II; Professional Papers: Correspondence: Harnischmacher, Paul and Marianne.
    - Drawings, 8
      - Büro (Nr. 233) [Leaf 205] (Aug 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Büro (Nr. 234) [Leaf 206] (Aug 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 8)
      - Büro (Nr. 235) [Leaf 207] (Aug 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Map-case 75)
      - Büro (Nr. 236) [Leaf 208] (Aug 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 8)
      - Büro (Nr. 237) [Leaf 209] (Aug 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 24)
      - Büro (Nr. 238) [Leaf 210] (Aug 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 8)
      - Tisch der Sekretärin (Nr. 240) [Leaf 211] (2 Oct 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 8)
      - Tisch der Sekretärin (Nr. 248) [Leaf 212] (14 Oct 1929), working drawing (originals); in German; 1 (Oversize 8)
    - Photographs, 3
      - Large office with table and wall units, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - Large office with table and wall units [Slide 392], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - Small office with desk and cabinets, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - HARVARD UNIVERSITY, BIOLOGY AND CHEMISTRY BUILDING, Cambridge, MA (1968-1971) (not built). Marcel Breuer and Robert F. Gatje, Architects. [Educational], (Alternate names: Robinson Hall)
    - Drawings, 220
      - Courtyard perspective, presentation drawings (originals); Larry Perron, artist; graphite on illustration board, 26.25 x 30 in.; 1 (Map-case 118, Folder 8)
      - Detail perspective, presentation drawings (originals); Larry Perron, artist; graphite on illustration board, 26.25 x 30 in.; 1 (Map-case 118, Folder 9)
      - Large format film negatives for creation of presentation sheets/sets, presentation drawings (reproductions); 12 (Tube 1439)
      - Perspective, presentation drawings (reproductions); photostat; 1 (Tube 1440)
      - Schematic design (Oct 1969) (Sheet Nos. 1-12 and overlays): Floor plans, sections, elevations, façade details, perspectives, presentation drawings (originals); 16 (Tube 1440)
      - Schematic design (Oct 1969) (Sheet Nos. 1-12): Floor plans, sections, elevations, façade details, perspectives, presentation drawings (reproductions); 13 (Tube 1440)
      - Site plans (Nov-Dec 1969), design development drawings (originals); 3 (Tube 1440)
      - Design development drawings (Jul-Aug 1969), design development drawings (originals); includes schematic elevations and panel studies, schematic sections for lecture hall layout; 96 (Tube 1441)
      - Preliminary schemes (Sep-Oct 1969), design development drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; 52 (Tube 1443)
      - Existing building / conditions, design development drawings (reproductions); photostats; 25 (Tube 1443)
    - Project files
      - Architect's report (1969) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Area calculations (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - Building codes (1969) (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - Contract (1969) (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Client (1968-1971), William Gardiner, Deputy Director, Dept. of Buildings and Grounds; Ronald Vanelli, Chemistry Dept., Building Committee Co-Chair (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Suppliers (1969-1970), inquiries with product literature (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Financial documents (1969-1970), cost estimates by John O. Meadows Associates (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda (1969-1970), Includes minutes of a 1970 Harvard Building Committee meeting (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - Transmittal (1969) (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, 16
      - Brookhaven National Lab: Floor plans, drawings, plan; corridor scheme and reference drawings; photocopies; 4 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - HARVARD YARD PROJECT, Cambridge, MA (1941) (not built) [Educational], (Alternate names: Redesigning Harvard Yard)
    - Published material, See Professional Papers: Scrapbooks and clippings: Brown scrapbook (2).
  - HAUS AM HORN, Weimar, Germany (1923-1925). [Exhibition structures], (Alternate names: Bauhaus Weimar exhibition house)
    The Haus am Horn was designed by George Muche, with interiors by Bauhaus workshops, for the 1923 Bauhaus Weimar exhibition (Bauhaus Ausstellung Weimar). Breuer collaborated on interior designs and furnishings for the Living room, one of the bedrooms and possibly part of the kitchen.
    - Published material, See Professional Papers: Scrapbooks and clippings: Blue scrapbook (1).
    - Photographs, 7
      - Bed (lemonwood and walnut, Haus-am-Horn), finished project, detail; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      - Bedroom axonometric drawing, drawings, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      - Bedroom axonometric drawing, drawings, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      - Bedroom dressing table [Slide 672], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-4)
      - Kitchen, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      - Kitchen, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 119, Folder 18)